Hi there, I am Eddie
Our community is called EddieHub
We believe that collaboration comes first and code comes second
We are an inclusive open source community that focuses on supporting each other
No matter where you are in your journey
Remember even if you only have 1 month experience
There is someone where you were 1 month ago
Helping others is a great way to learn and grow your network
We have my YouTube where you will find lots of tutorials about open source and GitHub
I also do live streams getting you involved in open source and finding you the green squares
Also, I bring awesome guests on there to hang out with us
We also have a GitHub organisation that you can
join
Just raise an issue on the support repo with the type "invite me to the organisations"
And the GitHub Action will do all the magic and
do all the rest, and send you an invitation
Remember if you would like other people to see you are part of our organisation
You have to make it public on your profile, only you can do that
We have many projects in our GitHub organisation from Discord bots written in typescript to
react frontends
And everything in between
If you want to get involved our community will help
you
You can also get your open source project review by the community and by me
And you guessed it by raising an issue on our support repo with the issue type "review
my open
source project" If you want to chat between YouTube videos
and live streams and your open source green squares
We also have a Discord where you
can come and
join the
conversation
With many exciting things going on
and so much more to come
If you want to learn more about open source,
collaborate and improve your technical and your communication
skills
Join our community to accelerate your career
Looking forward to chatting
with
you
soon